fuseclick.com 2017-06-29

# FuseClick | Mobile Performance Marketing SaaS Software

When using the FuseClick website and service located at [www.fuseclick.com](https://www.fuseclick.com/)(listed as "Site"), the following privacy policies and rights remain in effect. At all times, FuseClick will protect any personal identifiable information it obtains. This privacy policy is designed to give you a better understanding about the information we collect and how this information will be used at all times. All information obtained by FuseClick is used solely for the use of the services on our website. 

#### In order to continue using our website, you must agree to the following:

1\. You accept the terms of this privacy policy and the use of cookies on the website.  
2\. You agree this is a blanket policy and agree to any future updates of this policy.  
3\. You agree to routinely review any updates to the policy and allow FuseClick to notify you of changes.  
4\. If you do not agree with these terms, you agree to not become a subscriber to the website or to use it in any form.  

#### Privacy Policies Used in Connection with Your Subscription

Affiliates who join the affiliate program are to use the links provided through the website. These are provided to you through the services section of the website. All affiliate information is stored in a password protected portal on the website. FuseClick will not access this information, unless you have submitted a request for us to do so. It is at your sole discretion to review and upload to the applicable areas of our subscriber website. Do not give out your information or access to these sections of the website. To better monitor traffic, we do use anonymous transfer data through cookies, which are placed in the subscriber section of our website. We are not responsible for the collection, storage and/or use of the collected data in the subscription portion of our website. 

#### Personally Identifiable Information

When you sign up to become a subscriber, FuseClick collects personally identifiable information. This is used to identify you as a person or an entity. This information may include name, business name, business title, personal and business related phone numbers, mailing addresses, credit cards and other information. All these items are deemed sensitive information and will be closely guarded as it is listed in the Privacy Policy section. 

If you apply for any open positons through FuseClick, we will collect information about you. This includes your name, email address, phone number and a resume. This information is only used to review you for the position you’ve applied for and to determine if you are a strong candidate for the position. Your information will be used for no other purposes. 

Any job postings you share with a friend will collect their name and address. This information is used for a one-time e-mail to invite them. The information you’ve entered will be used for no other purposes. 

#### Non-Personally Identifiable Information

At times, we will collect non-personally identifiable information when you use our website. This will include information about your browser and operating system. We will also collect information on the internet service provider you are accessing our website with. This information is only used to help us improve the design and content of the website, so we can better enhance your experience. We will not use this information for any other purposes. 

#### SOCIAL MEDIA (FEATURES) AND WIDGETS

FuseClick uses Social Media Features to help share pages and improve interaction. This features collects an IP address and the pages you have visited. A cookie is then enabled on your device. All widgets and Social Media Widgets are provided through companies outside of the website. It is important you review the privacy policy of each to gain a better idea of how your information is used. 

#### FACEBOOK CONNECT OR OTHER OPENID PROVIDER

FuseClick allows you to use Facebook Connect or an Open ID to access our website. These features allow you to instantly access your account. They will contain personal information like name and address and will populate forms instantly. When using Facebook Connect and similar services, please note they will maintain your activities you use on the website and may share information with others within your network. 

#### Cookies and Web Beacons

In order to provide you with the best experience on the website, FuseClick uses cookies. If you do not agree to the use of cookies and our services, you are unable to use our website. Cookies are small packets of data that we store on your computer. These cookies are used to help store the preferences you have on our website. They also give us a better understanding of how you use the website, so we can provide you with a better experience. Some browsers allow you to block cookies or warn you when they are used. 

If you attempt to access an area of the website where cookies are required, you will be notified. It is important to setup your browser to help you accept these cookies. If you are not certain of how to do this on your individual browser, you can click on the help option in its menu. You may also visit [www.cookiecentral.com](http://www.cookiecentral.com/) in order to learn more about cookies, including how they are used and what can and cannot be done with a cookie. 

Please note any third party cookies are not covered by our privacy policy. 

Third party cookies and tracking tools on our website are collected through other Web beacons. These might occur through web bugs, pixel tags or Clear GIFs. Use of these items on our website are not protected under this policy and we are unable to determine what data is obtained. 

FuseClick does utilize retargeting campaigns with their cookie to help improve your interaction on the website. If you would like to opt-out of this feature, please follow the procedure at [www.fuseclick.com/privacy](https://www.fuseclick.com/privacy). 

#### Use of Information

FuseClick uses personally identifiable information in a few ways:  
1\. To send you information in regards to your FuseClick Subscription of Services.  
2\. To track your compliance with our Services Agreement.  
3\. For the validation, suppression, feedback and content improvement of normal use of our website.  
You agree we may contact you at any time we deem appropriate to continue using our Services or requesting additional information about our products and services. 

#### Information Sharing

FuseClick will never sell, share or rent your personally identifiable information to others. This includes the information of your child. FuseClick does require any children under the age of 18 to only access the website under the consent of their parents. Parents then agree to disclosure of personal information of their child to third party websites. However, we do not give the information of anyone's collected on our website without their consent. Examples of services we do provide information to include credit card processing, customer service, Subscription Services, billing companies and any other business required to do standard business with you. 

FuseClick will also share personally identifiable information in the following cases.  
1\. A subpoena from a court has demanded the information. We will in good faith provide all required documentation. Our goal is to protect your safety and the safety of others involved.  
2\. Our company goes through a merger, sale or information is being used for stock assets as required by law.  
3\. If you are in clear violation of our policies.  
4\. In the event of a dispute.  
5\. FuseClick will also provide this information in the case it is necessary to protect its rights, or the rights of others against liability.  

#### International Transfer of Data

When using our Services, we may transfer some information about you and other Subscription Users to other third parties. This includes End Users who are located within the European Union and those in areas of the world where governing data collection is required. You content to have your information transferred as required. This includes any personal information covered in the Privacy Policy. 

#### Data Retention

Information is retained as long as your account is active, or it is needed to provide services to our website. If you want to cancel your account, we ask you contact us at [support@fuseclick.com](mailto:support@fuseclick.com). We will retain any information necessary for legal disputes and to enforce agreements or resolve disputes. 

#### Third Party Links

Our site may contain links to Third Party Websites. Please note, FuseClick is not responsible for any of the privacy practices of these websites. When you visit any website, please take note of the information they collect. You are solely responsible for the use of the information from this website. 

#### Minors

FuseClick encourages parents and guardians to monitor their children's time online. They should routinely review the information. FuseClick will not collect any information about anyone under the age of 18 knowingly. If they determine they have this information, it will be removed at once. 

At all times, we will strive to protect any minors using our website. Under Law, we will comply with all Federal, State and International requirements as part of the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998. 

For the purposes of this provision, the definitions of “personal information” and “children” (and their translational and linguistic equivalents) are defined by the jurisdiction where the Customer is operating. 

#### Your Employees

By accepting the terms of our Privacy Policy, you also give use the same authority to govern your employees if any who access our website through your account. They are further held to the same terms which are listed in this privacy agreement. 

#### Security

We will do all we can to protect and safeguard the information of our users. When you submit personally identifiable information to us on you are protected both online and offline. During our registration you are asked to provide us with banking information. To protect you, we use a SSL encryption software to better protect your information. As we do your information is better protected. 

We will do everything in our power to safeguard your information and to keep it secure at all times. However, we cannot guarantee all information you submit online outside of secure areas is protected. Any information you place on our website is done so at your own risk. All information on our website is accessible only from limited third party applications and employees. If we learn there is a security breach at any time, we will notify you as required by law. 

When you use our website, you are doing so with consent that this is done at your own risk. 

#### Deleting and Updating Your Information

To have your personally identifiable information removed or deleted from our system, you need to contact us. You can do this by:  
1\. Sending a certified letter to Iferox Limited, 15/B CHEUK NANG PLAZA 250, HENNESSY RD, HONG KONG.  
2\. Submitting a request via e-mail to [support@fuseclick.com](mailto:support@fuseclick.com).  

Regardless of the method of contact, please allow us 30 days to respond to your request. Within this timeframe, we will process your request. To protect you, your privacy, and security, we will verify your identity before removing, deleting or updating your information through a formal request. 

#### Opting Out of Receiving E-mail

If decide to, you can stop receiving e-mails from us at any time. Please send us an e-mail to [support@fuseclick.com](mailto:support@fuseclick.com). It may take us a few days, but we will remove your e-mail address at your request. 

#### INFORMATION RELATED TO DATA COLLECTED THROUGH THE FUSECLICKPLATFORM

FuseClick will collect information as request by our clients. We do not have a direct relationship with how this information is processed. 

#### CHOICE

Per the request of our clients, we will give information on our customers. If you receive an interaction from a client of ours and would like to stop receiving communication, please let them know. 

#### SERVICE PROVIDER, SUB-PROCESSORS/ONWARD TRANSFER

FuseClick may transfer your information to companies who help us to provide you with the best experience possible. When your information is transferred it is covered under their policies. Please take the time to review the service agreements of our clients. 

#### ACCESS TO DATA CONTROLLED BY OUR CLIENTS

FuseClick has no direct relationship with anyone whose personal data we process. If someone wishes to seek access or amend information, they should do so by sending us information at once. Any client who wishes to have their information removed must send a request to FuseClick. We will respond to requests within 30 days. 

#### DATA RETENTION

FuseClick will keep personal data on behalf of our clients as long as it is necessary to help our clients or to comply with legal obligations. This information may also be kept to resolve disputes and to further enforce our agreements. 

#### Notification of alterations

All changes to our information practices is updated on this privacy statement. Any material changes made will be notified to you by email (it is sent to the email address mentioned in your account) or through a notice on this site, before the change is implemented. We thus suggest you keep on reviewing this page to learn about the latest changes and information on our privacy practices. 

In case we make actual changes on the method of collecting personal information from children aged below 13, we ensure our client informs the parents to get verifiable consent from them for the new utilization of the child’s personal details. 

#### Safe Harbor

FuseClick abides with the US-EU Safe Harbor structure and the US-Swiss Safe Harbor structure set by the US Department of Commerce about collecting, using and retaining personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. 

FuseClick certifies that it follows the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, onward transfer, choice, security, access, enforcement and data integrity. For more about the Safe Harbor program and to see FuseClick recognition, visit http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/. 

#### Contact Us

Any queries about this Privacy Policy, or if any more information is needed about our privacy practices, just contact us at [support@fuseclick.com](mailto:support@fuseclick.com) or Iferox Limited, 15/B CHEUK NANG PLAZA 250, HENNESSY RD, HONG KONG.
